http://www.fifehouse.org/privacy-information/

Performers for Life
Hold A Fundraiser!
Donate
Ways To Give
Become A Fife House Builder!
Performers for Life
Hold A Fundraiser!
Donate
Ways To Give
Become A Fife House Builder!
Purpose Statement
Fife House respects your privacy. We protect your personal information and adhere to all legislative requirements with respect to protecting privacy. The information you provide will be used to deliver services and to keep you informed and up-to-date on the activities of Fife House, including programs, services, special events, funding needs, opportunities to volunteer or to give, open houses and other periodic contacts. If at any time you wish to be removed from any of these contacts, simply contact the Development Department at 416-205-9888, or via email at privacy@fifehouse.org, and we will gladly accommodate your request.
Fife House Privacy Policy Statement
The following policy provides information on how Fife House collects, uses and safeguards any personal information. This policy may change from time to time. Please reread this policy periodically.
Our Commitment
Fife House is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of its employees, members, residents, clients, volunteers, donors and other stakeholders. Fife House values the trust of those we deal with, and of the public at large, and recognize that maintaining this trust requires that Fife House be transparent and accountable in how we treat the information that is shared with us.
During the course of our various projects and activities, Fife House frequently gathers and utilizes personal information. Anyone from whom we collect such information should expect that it will be carefully protected and that any use or other dealing with this information is subject to consent. Fife House’s privacy practices are designed to achieve this.
Defining Personal Information
Personal information is any information that can be used to distinguish, identify or contact a specific individual. This information can include an individual’s opinions or beliefs, as well as, facts about, or related to, the individual. Exceptions: business contact information and certain publicly available information, such as names, addresses and telephone numbers as published in telephone directories, are not considered personal information.
Where an individual uses his or her home contact information as business contact information as well, Fife House considers that the contact information provided is business contact information, and is not therefore subject to protection as personal information.
Privacy Practices
Personal information gathered by Fife House is kept in confidence. Our personnel are authorized to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for he reason/s for which it was obtained. Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered. Fife House also takes measures to ensure the integrity of this information is maintained and to prevent its being lost and/or destroyed.
We use password protocols and encryption software to protect personal and other information that we receive when an event or service is requested and/or paid for online.
We collect, use and disclose personal information only for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in light of the circumstances. We routinely offer individuals we deal with the opportunity to opt not to have their information share for purposes beyond those for which it was explicitly collected.
Fife House does not trade its mailing lists with other charities or organizations.
If at any time you wish to correct, update or remove your personal information from our databases, please call the Development Department at 416-205-9888 or e-mail privacy@fifehouse.org.
Update of Privacy Policies
Fife House regularly reviews our privacy practices for our various activities and updates our policy. Please check Fife House’s website, and all other places where our privacy policy is posted, on an on-going basis for information on our most up-to-date practices.
Contact Information
Questions, concerns and/or complaints relating to Fife House’s privacy policy on the treatment of personal information should be directed to the Chief Privacy Officer (CPO) who is the Director of Development and Communications, by phone at 416-205-9888 or by e-mail at privacy@fifehouse.org.
Further information on privacy and your rights in regard to your personal information maybe be found on the website of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada at www.privcom.gc.ca.
Site Map
|
Contact Us
|
Privacy Information
© 2020 Fife House Foundation, Inc.
